‪We haven't seen these guys in a while.
‪ONE SUMMER DAY IN SEOUL
‪-Hello.
‪We're the hosts
‪of ‪Better Late Than Single‪.
‪-I'm Car, the garden.
‪-And I'm Lee Eun-ji.
‪Welcome to the show.
‪Today, we'll take participants
‪from Season Two
‪and send these kids
‪on an avatar blind date.
‪Did you just say "kids"?
‪-We'll send these guys
‪-Right.
‪-on an avatar blind date.
‪-Yes.
‪Apparently, they're still single.
‪-What?
‪-As expected.
‪But if they had gone on blind dates
‪and put in some effort…
‪-Nope. Not at all.
‪-At least one…
‪"Nope"?
‪Nope. Not a chance.
‪-By the way…
‪-Yes?
‪Do these kids know
‪they're going on avatar blind dates?
‪Wait, not kids. Do they know?
‪My understanding is that they don't.
‪All they know is
‪that they're going on a blind date.
‪Okay, got it.
‪They probably have no idea
‪that the past season's participants
‪will be taking part
‪-in this.
‪-Probably not.
‪Hello.
‪Oh, hello.
‪-Hello.
‪Did you eventually find love?
‪I was shocked because you're so pretty.
‪I have this fantasy
‪of being wrapped in someone's arms.
‪Welcome.
‪ETERNAL SINGLES' A/S BLIND DATE
‪Are you willing
‪to get in touch with me after this?
‪BETTER LATE THAN SINGLE: AFTER SERVICE
‪AVATAR BLIND DATE
‪FIRST BLIND DATE
‪HAN SU-JI
‪SEASON 2, STUDIED IN THE UK
‪I liked Su-ji in Season Two
‪because it was like
‪watching her come into her own.
‪-"I'm going to do what I like."
‪-Yes.
‪-That was their actual goal, right?
‪-Right.
‪-Not worrying about what others think.
‪-Exactly.
‪You need to be happy
‪to have the capacity to love someone else.
‪-Wow, are you…
‪-Right?
‪Are you taking lessons on this stuff?
‪-Oh, hello.
‪-Hello.
‪-Goodness, hello.
‪-Oh, hello.
‪-Hello.
‪-Goodness, hello.
‪-Nice to meet you.
‪-Hello.
‪Yes, hello.
‪KIM SEUNG-LI
‪SEASON 1, STUDIED OVERSEAS
‪Please take a seat.
‪-Hello.
‪SU-JI & SEUNG-LI
‪-Nice to meet you.
‪-Likewise.
‪-Glad to meet you.
‪-Glad to meet you too.
‪-I think Su-ji knows who he is.
‪-Yes, she does.
‪Since he was in Season One.
‪Did I keep you waiting?
‪No, I just got here.
‪Mind if I take a sip of water?
‪No, go ahead.
‪That was good.
‪He asked first before taking a sip.
‪I think Seung-li feels intimidated.
‪-Are you okay?
‪-What?
‪-It's very hot today, so…
‪-It is, isn't it?
‪-I'm okay.
‪May I ask your name?
‪My name is Han Su-ji.
‪-Han Su-ji?
‪-Yes, Su-ji.
‪My name is Kim Seung-li.
‪-It's nice to meet you.
‪-Nice to meet you.
‪Have you been on many blind dates?
‪No, only once.
‪-Once?
‪-Just once.
‪What about you?
‪Me? Well…
‪Maybe 14 blind dates?
‪Gosh, that's a lot.
‪What were they like?
‪It was really awkward at first, but now…
‪-I'm still looking for the right person,
‪-Right.
‪-which is why I'm here on this blind date.
‪-Oh, yeah?
‪-Oh, Su-ji seems interested.
‪-You're right.
‪What's your take on her look?
‪Does she seem genuinely interested?
‪-She looks curious.
‪-Curious?
‪Do you mind if I ask your age?
‪Oh, I…
‪-I was born in 2000.
‪-In 2000?
‪-And how old are you?
‪-I was born in 1998.
‪-So a two-year gap?
‪-Yes.
‪-A two-year gap.
‪-Right.
‪Would you like to drink something?
‪Can we order?
‪Can we order something to drink?
‪What I like so much right now
‪is that Seung-li is taking the lead.
‪This is the first time
‪since the show started
‪that someone asked,
‪"Would you like something?"
‪Seung-li is a pretty big guy,
‪-but he's shy, which could be charming.
‪-Totally.
‪Do you want to say something now?
‪Like, "This is Car, the garden."
‪Seung-li, this is Car, the garden.
‪Pretend you don't hear me.
‪You're on an avatar blind date.
‪Do as I say.
‪-Got it?
‪-Yes.
‪No need to answer.
‪Okay.
‪SU-JI IS CLUELESS
‪I lived overseas.
‪-I lived overseas.
‪-I see.
‪So I like people I can click with
‪in that regard.
‪In what regard?
‪I really like clicking
‪with someone like this.
‪Anyway, it's nice to meet you. Welcome.
‪-Anyway, it's nice to meet you. Welcome.
‪-Likewise.
‪-Thank you.
‪-Sure.
‪Do you speak English?
‪A little bit.
‪A little bit?
‪Are you good at English?
‪Actually, I ‪only‪ speak English.
‪English is easier.
‪-English is a bit easier than Korean.
‪-Really?
‪Yes.
‪I see.
‪Do you want to speak in English?
‪-Right now?
‪-In English?
‪In English?
‪I'd appreciate your understanding.
‪Oh, you speak British English.
‪-I lived in the UK.
‪-You're fluent.
‪When I was very young, that is.
‪I don't know much about British English.
‪I don't know how to speak British English.
‪Sorry about that.
‪It's okay.
‪"Sorry about that."
‪-Thank you.
‪-Tell the server, "Thank you, sir."
‪Is this an act?
‪Shall we clink? Thank you.
‪-This is good.
‪-It's good.
‪This is really good.
‪Call for the server. Say, "Waiter!"
‪Who actually calls out, "Waiter"?
‪-It's 2026, for crying out loud.
‪-Say, "Excuse me, waiter!"
‪Excuse me, waiter!
‪This coffee is black?
‪How do you like it?
‪-It's good.
‪-It is?
‪Yes.
‪I think it's good too.
‪I don't usually like coffee,
‪but this is good.
‪Oh, really?
‪-Oh, really?
‪-Yes.
‪-I see.
‪He's even copying "I see."
‪Su-ji, were you perhaps
‪in ‪Better Late Than Single‪?
‪Were you perhaps
‪in ‪Better Late Than Single 2‪?
‪-Yes.
‪-Really?
‪-I had a feeling.
‪-And you were in Season One.
‪That's right. How did you know?
‪-You know who I am.
‪-Because I watched it.
‪Oh, yeah?
‪-You were born in 2000.
‪-Yes.
‪Do you find it easy to speak casually?
‪It doesn't matter to me.
‪What do you prefer?
‪-Shall we speak casually?
‪-Sure.
‪-So it's more comfortable?
‪They're dropping honorifics?
‪Is it normal to start speaking casually
‪so fast on a blind date?
‪What's your ideal type?
‪My ideal type?
‪-Looks-wise, first.
‪-Looks-wise?
‪I like guys taller than me.
‪-How tall are we talking about?
‪-I'm 168 cm tall, so…
‪-You're 168 cm tall?
‪-Maybe 167 or 168.
‪Somewhere in between.
‪-So maybe someone at least 10 cm taller.
‪-Oh, 10 cm?
‪I have this fantasy
‪of being wrapped in someone's arms.
‪Do you want to check our height?
‪-Can you stand up? I'm curious.
‪-Okay.
‪Oh my gosh, Car.
‪-Look at them.
‪-Let's see.
‪What's going on?
‪How tall are you?
‪-Taller than 180 cm.
‪-Really?
‪-Hey, you're tall.
‪-I have low heels on right now.
‪-You're pretty tall.
‪-Kind of like this?
‪-You're tall.
‪-Very nice.
‪What?
‪Seung-li has changed a bit.
‪What else other than height?
‪Well…
‪To be honest, I…
‪There are softies and tough guys, right?
‪I kind of like softies.
‪-You like softies?
‪-Yes.
‪-It's just an ideal type, though.
‪-Right.
‪I think I'm the opposite of that.
‪Are you a tough guy through and through?
‪-No, it's not that.
‪-Then what is it?
‪I'm a softie pretending to be a tough guy.
‪-I think that's the type I am.
‪-Really?
‪What do you think of this type?
‪-A softie pretending to be tough.
‪-It's not the other way around?
‪-A tough guy pretending…
‪-Hey, I can see you thinking.
‪Just answer.
‪Don't think.
‪Answer me right now.
‪-Tough… Okay, I'm a softie.
‪-What are you saying?
‪I'm a softie, not a tough guy.
‪No tough guy here.
‪-You're a softie pretending to be tough?
‪-Yes.
‪Is there anything else?
‪Well, personality-wise…
‪-I love watching anime.
‪-Anime?
‪So I'd like someone
‪who I can share hobbies with.
‪So you don't like being active?
‪I play badminton
‪-and tennis.
‪-Tennis?
‪I'm not good at using my feet.
‪-But I can use my hands.
‪-Your hands?
‪I'm the total opposite.
‪-I'm really good at soccer.
‪-Oh, really?
‪If you watch me play soccer,
‪-you might fall for me.
‪-Is that so?
‪I'll be in big trouble, then.
‪I'll get in trouble if I watch.
‪There's a soccer ball there, right?
‪Go bring that ball.
‪Hey, there's a ball!
‪That's random.
‪What's a soccer ball doing here?
‪That's so random.
‪I can't hold myself back
‪when I see a ball.
‪Gosh, that's so cringe.
‪Actually, I can't hold myself back
‪-Seriously?
‪-when I see a ball.
‪Want to see?
‪Are you showing me a special trick?
‪Do it one at a time.
‪"One, two, three… What comes after this?"
‪-Hold on.
‪-Show me.
‪One, two, three, four…
‪What comes after this?
‪What do you mean?
‪That was my special trick.
‪You're really good.
‪-You're out of breath?
‪-Sorry.
‪-I got excited.
‪-You're breathless?
‪-I'm sorry.
‪-Are you okay?
‪-I got carried away.
‪-You did?
‪You really can't control yourself
‪when you see a ball.
‪I get excited.
‪Wow.
‪That's fascinating.
‪Su-ji, what if I had been in Season Two?
‪What if I had been in Season Two?
‪-In Season Two?
‪-Yes.
‪You have a slightly different vibe
‪from the guys in Season Two.
‪-Really?
‪-Yes.
‪You're very different from them,
‪so I think you would've done well.
‪Is that a good thing?
‪-Of course, it's good.
‪-Really?
‪I just meant that you would've done well.
‪-Is there anyone
‪-Yes?
‪from the show you still think about?
‪In what way?
‪In a romantic way.
‪In a romantic way?
‪It looks like she does.
‪She still thinks about someone.
‪I don't think so.
‪You mean, you don't want to answer?
‪No, I mean,
‪-I'm not ‪really‪ thinking about anyone.
‪-I see.
‪No, I mean,
‪-I'm not ‪really‪ thinking about anyone.
‪-I see.
‪Oh, so there isn't anyone.
‪That's a relief.
‪Because…
‪I'm about to enter your heart.
‪That's a relief.
‪Why is that a relief?
‪Because…
‪You're about to say something weird.
‪I'm about to enter your heart.
‪Oh, yeah?
‪Can I?
‪You almost entered it.
‪Is there room for me?
‪-Is there room for me?
‪-Yeah.
‪-There is?
‪-For whom?
‪Is there room for me in your heart?
‪I said you almost entered it.
‪I can't believe
‪he's following all my commands.
‪He actually said, "Knock, knock."
‪Knock, knock, my foot.
‪Like he's telling a knock-knock joke.
‪-This is for you.
‪-That's random.
‪-What is it?
‪-A gift.
‪-Seriously, it's a gift.
‪-Really?
‪Are you serious?
‪-Yes, I paid for it myself.
‪-Oh my, thank you.
‪Seriously?
‪Thank you.
‪I think it's nice,
‪but I don't have anything for you.
‪-I should've gotten something.
‪-It's okay.
‪I met you. That's enough for me.
‪-Really?
‪-Yeah.
‪Let's meet up again.
‪Sounds good. I'll give you a gift then.
‪Will you meet me afterward?
‪If you want.
‪-Really?
‪-Yeah.
‪But you don't seem interested.
‪-What are you doing?
‪-Should I ask for your number?
‪My number?
‪Are you saying you want my number?
‪You're asking for it?
‪There you go.
‪Thanks.
‪Now say that you'll message her later
‪and leave the room.
‪Okay, then I'll message you later.
‪Oh, so I have to wait for your message?
‪Well, I plan to message you right away.
‪Really?
‪-Message…
‪-You're just leaving like this?
‪-Yeah.
‪-Gone like the wind?
‪-I've got things to do.
‪-That's a shame.
‪You're not taking this?
‪-This?
‪-You're nuts about it.
‪I'll take it as a keepsake.
‪-I'll get in touch.
‪-Take care. I had fun.
‪-Bye.
‪-I'll really message you, okay?
‪Okay.
‪Jeez, what is this?
‪This is just a comedy show!
‪Come on, Car.
‪Can't we be normal about this?
‪What's the point of having me here then?
‪You should've called In-guk for that.
‪You can't call me here
‪and expect a normal blind date.
‪I've never been on a normal blind date.
‪I'm not any better than they are.
‪At least these guys
‪have gone on blind dates.
‪I've never been on one before!
‪How can you expect me to do it
‪when I don't know how?
‪One thing's for sure.
‪He looks much better in person
‪than he did on the show.
‪But it seems like
‪he has two personalities.
‪That makes me a little bit hesitant.
‪But I had a good time,
‪meeting him in person.
‪I'll probably see him again.
‪I don't think that's a big deal.
‪When I first walked in,
‪I was really surprised
‪to see a pretty lady sitting there.
‪After talking to her for a while,
‪my interest in her grew.
‪I promised Su-ji
‪I'd message her when I left.
‪It might sound like
‪I'm quick to fall in love,
‪but I really liked her.
‪I think I truly liked her.
‪I'm being genuine here.
‪WHO'S UP NEXT FOR A BLIND DATE?
‪Hey, not bad.
‪Look at Jae-seo.
‪-He looks better with a bit more weight.
‪-Agreed.
‪Jae-seo looks younger.
‪-He looks like a college student.
‪-He looks youthful.
‪KIM JAE-SEO, SEASON 2
‪GAME DEVELOPER, KAIST GRADUATE
‪-Wow, Yi Do.
‪-She looks great.
‪Hey, they're matching.
‪-Yi Do looks particularly pretty today.
‪-They're matching.
‪They're wearing matching shirts.
‪YI DO, SEASON 1
‪GEOGRAPHY INSTRUCTOR, SNU GRADUATE
‪For this blind date,
‪we didn't give Jae-seo an earpiece.
‪-So he can't hear anything Car says.
‪-Right.
‪JAE-SEO IS UNAWARE
‪THIS IS AN AVATAR BLIND DATE
‪-Hello.
‪-Oh, hello.
‪Hello.
‪BEFORE SEASON 2 LAUNCH
‪YI DO DOESN'T KNOW JAE-SEO
‪-Hello.
‪-Shall we sit?
‪-Yes.
‪Nice to meet you.
‪Actually, in the pre-production interview,
‪I was asked which Season One participant
‪came closest to my ideal type.
‪And I remember saying it was Yi Do.
‪So I was very surprised
‪to have her on the date.
‪Nice to meet you.
‪Sorry, I'm a bit flustered.
‪JAE-SEO & YI DO
‪-Excuse me?
‪-I'm a bit flustered.
‪Yi Do, this is Eun-ji.
‪This is an avatar blind date.
‪When I tell you to do something,
‪you must do exactly as I say, okay?
‪Hello. My name is Yi Do.
‪-Pleased to meet you.
‪-Likewise.
‪I'm Kim Jae-seo.
‪Kim Jae-seo.
‪May I ask your age?
‪-I was born in 1994.
‪-I see.
‪You were born in 1998, right?
‪Wow, you look so young for your age!
‪You look so young for your age.
‪-Really?
‪-Yes, I thought
‪-you might be younger than me.
‪-I see.
‪I'm not sure if I should say this,
‪but you look much different
‪in person.
‪You look so pretty
‪that I thought you were someone else.
‪Sorry about that.
‪Thank you.
‪He's being a bit extra now.
‪It's really interesting to see
‪we're wearing matching outfits.
‪-Oh, wait.
‪-Yes?
‪We're wearing matching shirts. Did you…
‪No, I really didn't.
‪-Did you know?
‪-Not at all.
‪-I didn't know.
‪-Really?
‪Did someone tell you
‪-to wear that shirt?
‪-No, not at all.
‪-What's going on?
‪-Wow.
‪It feels like fate.
‪It feels like fate…
‪-Right off the bat?
‪-No?
‪Right off the bat?
‪-I guess it's possible.
‪-I mean, we have a common ground.
‪-You know?
‪-Right.
‪He's totally loving this.
‪May I ask what your job is?
‪Well, my job is…
‪I work for a gaming company.
‪-Really?
‪-Yes.
‪Do you play games by any chance?
‪-I don't think you do.
‪-Well, may I ask what game
‪-you worked on?
‪-It's called ‪PUBG: Battlegrounds‪.
‪-What?
‪-You know it, right?
‪That's amazing!
‪I really like ‪PUBG: Battlegrounds‪!
‪-Do you play?
‪-I'm serious. You go like this.
‪You know what I mean, right?
‪-You go like this, right?
‪-Yes.
‪I really like that game.
‪Yi Do's real personality is coming out.
‪Then do you work in Seongsu?
‪No, the company is moving there.
‪Then do you work near
‪Seoul Nat'l. Univ. of Education station?
‪No, our headquarters is located in Seocho.
‪-Seocho?
‪-Right.
‪Oh, that's right.
‪She teaches Korean geography.
‪Geography. It's all about geography.
‪Our geography expert.
‪Jae-seo, which university did you go to?
‪If you don't mind me asking,
‪which university
‪did you attend?
‪Well, my understanding is
‪that you also attended
‪a special-purpose high school.
‪Yes, that's right.
‪I graduated from a science high school.
‪-Oh, did you…
‪-After that,
‪I majored in Mathematics at KAIST.
‪-You studied math?
‪-Yes.
‪I majored in pure mathematics.
‪Of course,
‪I found mathematics interesting,
‪but I actually chose it because
‪it involved the least memorization.
‪He'll make wedding invites today.
‪He's ready to make them.
‪-I have a question.
‪-Yes?
‪Are you
‪a ‪Better Late Than Single 2‪ participant?
‪Am I wrong?
‪-You're right.
‪-I am?
‪Yes, that's why I was wondering…
‪I think we're both flustered right now.
‪Oh, I just heard
‪-that I was going on a blind date.
‪-Right.
‪-I see.
‪-I get it now.
‪I guess I let the cat out of the bag.
‪So did you eventually find love
‪in Eternal Singles' Village?
‪Well, I failed.
‪Same. Nice to meet you.
‪-We have another thing in common.
‪-Right.
‪So we're in the same boat.
‪I'm so jealous of the women in Season Two.
‪-I should've been there instead.
‪-What a shame.
‪I'm a little jealous
‪of the women in Season Two.
‪-What?
‪-Because you know…
‪Then I'm jealous of the men in Season One.
‪-How about that?
‪-Thank you.
‪I bet you get told
‪you're handsome all the time.
‪Don't people tell you
‪that you're handsome all the time?
‪No, not at all.
‪What? Not at all?
‪But after the show,
‪people have started telling me that.
‪Right, so…
‪Really? But you give off a tough guy vibe.
‪-I see.
‪-You have that cool look.
‪He's flustered right now.
‪I've heard something like that before,
‪but it wasn't necessarily
‪a positive comment.
‪Like how?
‪They say I'm more like a wild beast
‪-than a hunky, beastly man.
‪-What?
‪-What was that again?
‪-I shouldn't have said that.
‪Did you say wild beast?
‪Yes, that's what I heard.
‪But I think things have changed a bit.
‪You have thick eyebrows.
‪Do you mind if I touch them?
‪That's a good one. Nice job.
‪So…
‪I notice you have really thick eyebrows.
‪-Yes, I do.
‪-Is it okay
‪if I touch them?
‪-What?
‪-Your eyebrows…
‪-Yes?
‪-Are they real?
‪This is hilarious.
‪Your eyebrows…
‪-Yes?
‪-Are they real?
‪Yes, they are. It's not makeup.
‪You can touch them.
‪You don't mind?
‪-They just look so amazing.
‪-Yes, go ahead.
‪Wow, it's real hair.
‪-Of course, it's real hair.
‪-But many people fill in their brows.
‪Actually, I'm the opposite.
‪Mine are so bushy
‪that I have to trim them.
‪You have really large hands.
‪Can we compare?
‪Jeez, you'll give him a heart attack.
‪-Gosh, you have really large hands.
‪-My hands?
‪-Can we compare?
‪-Sure.
‪-You have really big hands.
‪-Yes.
‪Jae-seo is in trouble.
‪He's already in love.
‪I think he's in love.
‪He's on a collision course with love.
‪Tell her to sip some water
‪-and gargle.
‪-Yi Do, pick up the glass,
‪take a sip of water, and gargle.
‪Yeah, gargle.
‪-You seem really nervous.
‪-Yes, I am.
‪This is my first blind date
‪-since the show.
‪-Right.
‪Take a sip of water
‪-and gargle.
‪-Yes, do that.
‪Did someone tell you to do that?
‪No, I'm just really nervous right now.
‪I'm an instructor,
‪so I need to keep my throat hydrated.
‪How do you like this side of me, Jae-seo?
‪Are you perhaps disappointed?
‪Are you a little disappointed
‪after seeing this side of me?
‪I'd be disappointed
‪if you were doing this voluntarily.
‪-Right.
‪-But it feels like you're being forced to.
‪You're giving off this vibe,
‪like you're conflicted about it.
‪-Right.
‪-I can tell.
‪-I see.
‪-So I'm not disappointed.
‪That's a relief.
‪Thank you.
‪Are you interested
‪in getting to know me better?
‪-By the way…
‪-Yes?
‪-After today,
‪-Yes.
‪are you interested
‪in getting to know me better?
‪Oh, actually,
‪I wanted to say this first.
‪First off, ‪Better Late Than Single 2
‪will be out soon.
‪-Season Two, that is.
‪-Right.
‪I'd like you to watch it
‪because I've already seen you
‪in Season One.
‪So it feels a little unfair to you.
‪-I see.
‪-I think it'd be good for you
‪to see what kind of person I am,
‪what mistakes I made,
‪and what problems I had.
‪Second, after that…
‪I want to meet up with you
‪-where there are no cameras or mics.
‪-Really?
‪Then can I call you
‪after I watch the entire show?
‪I'd like that.
‪-Thank you.
‪-Oh, not at all.
‪-Thank you for being so kind to me.
‪-Sure.
‪But someone needs me right now.
‪-Oh, is this the end of the bit?
‪-So I have to go.
‪-That's right.
‪-Okay, got it.
‪-Thank you for today.
‪-Right.
‪-Nice meeting you.
‪-It was really nice
‪to meet you today.
‪Jae-seo doesn't want her to go.
‪He really doesn't.
‪Did he fall in love?
‪I thought he was cool.
‪Not only his looks,
‪but he also really seemed laid-back.
‪He gave off a mature, dependable vibe.
‪It'd be nice to see him again.
‪I'm open to the idea
‪of getting to know Jae-seo better.
‪I thought she was someone else at first.
‪She was much prettier than I thought.
‪I don't have much else to say
‪other than that.
‪She's much prettier in person.
‪Q. HOW WAS THE AVATAR BLIND DATE?
‪It was fun.
‪I was really nervous
‪about going on a blind date,
‪but I was able to enjoy it
‪because I caught on that it was
‪an avatar blind date from the start.
‪So, in a way, I thought it was good.
‪I was actually being sincere
‪toward the end of the blind date.
‪I'd really like to talk to her
‪away from the cameras and mics.
‪Subtitle translation by:
‪Jenny Kim